zerodha.net 2011-12-23

# ZERODHA PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY 

* * *

Zerodha Ltd. operates the web site accessible from the URL www.Zerodha.com (the 'Web Site').

Zerodha Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy and utilizing technology to give you the most powerful and safe online experience that you can get anywhere else.

Zerodha Ltd, does gather certain information that is provided by you to the Web Site. Zerodha Ltd. believes that by collecting this information it is able to provide you with a personalised web experience and assist its own sales team and advertisers in efficiently reaching an appropriate audience.

Zerodha Ltd. requests and collects minimum information it believes necessary to achieve this goal.

The following policy discloses information gathering and dissemination practices of Zerodha Ltd. for the Web Site:

Registration Data

The Web Site's registration form may require users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address), unique identifiers (like their PAN Number) and demographic information (like their pin code, age or income level). The Web Site uses customer contact information from the registration form to send the users information about Zerodha.com and promotional material from partners of Zerodha Ltd. and Zerodha.com. Unique identifiers (such as PAN numbers) are collected to verify the user's identity. Demographic and profile data is also collected at the Web Site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at the Web Site, showing them contents that we think they might be interested in, and display the contents according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Links and Co-Branded Sites

This site contains links to other Web Sites which have not necessarily been screened or reviewed by Zerodha.com. Zerodha Ltd. is neither responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such Web Sites nor shall we be held answerable for the inaccurate, inappropriate or offensive data, material, information, products and services that may be viewed on those sites.

Order Forms

The Web Site uses an order form for customers to request information, products and services. The Web Site collects visitors' contact information (like their e-mail address), unique identifiers (such as PAN numbers), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers) and demographic information (such as their pin code, age or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about Zerodha.com, and promotional material from some of Zerodha Ltd. and Zerodha.com partners to the visitors of the Web Site. VisitorsÂ’ contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as PAN numbers) are also collected from Web Site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Protection of your Data and Information

The privacy and protection of your data and information provided to us is of vital importance. Zerodha Ltd. strives to ensure the highest level of security and confidentiality of any information you share with us. Any personally identifiable information of the customers obtained by us shall not be used or shared other than for the purposes to which the customer consents. However security and confidentiality of information cannot always be guaranteed. Hence despite our utmost efforts to protect your personal information, Zerodha Ltd. and Zerodha.com cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through our online services. Such transmission of your personal information is done at your own risk.

Disclosure of Customer Information

Zerodha Ltd. and Zerodha.com shall not deliberately disclose customer's personally identifiable information to any unauthorized third party, save and except where such information shall be disclosed in good faith and for lawful purposes to protect the rights and property of Zerodha Ltd. and Zerodha.com.

Public Forums

The Web Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when disclosing any such information.

Supplemental Information

The Web Site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

Children’s Guidelines

The Web Site:

1.  DOES NOT collect online information from children without prior parental/guardian consent or parental/guardian notification, which serves as an opportunity   
     for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond   
     directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes;   
2.  DOES NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent;   
3.  DOES NOT distribute any personally identifiable information to third parties without prior parental consent;   
4.  DOES NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent;  
5.  DOES NOT entice children through the prospect of special games, prizes or other activities.
